# Tunde J Folorunsho | Software Developer (IT)

 $\ensuremath{\mathfrak{O}}$  London or West midland etc , manchester , willing to relocate

**3**07471013345 / 07424214340

Foltunde@gmail.com

## **Professional Profile**

I am a hardworking, reliable person with good time keeping skills and a good punctuality record. I enjoy learning and have the willingness to learn and acquire new skills. I ampolite, friendly, easy going and a good team player with a great ability to adapt to new or changing environments. couple with leadership experience has a branch managerunder a digital company, ability to adapt to a new technology.

## **Core Skills**

- Business support
- Communications
- Customer service
- Programming
- Campaign management

- Presentation
- Graphic design
- Data protection
- IT support
- Risk management

# **Career Summary**

Oct 2023- Present Tunde Digital World

May 2023 - Aug 2023 Netcom Training, Second line Engineer

April 2022 - Nov 2022 DHL Pepsico - Coventry, (IT)

Oct 2019- March 2022 A.G.G World Limited, Coventry Sales Manager

Feb 2017 - Nov 2021 Skynate Group, Nigeria, Manager

### **Education**

**Front-Web Developer.** | Bootcamp Edx. | Nov 2023 - March 2024 | JavaScript, Django, Python, Bootstrap, jQuery, API, React. Node.js etc.

**Software Developer.** | Code Institute. Dublin | Feb 2022 – March 2023 | HTML, CSS, Python, Django, Bootstrap, API, JavaScript etc.

**Netcom certificate / Cisco Network certificate** | Netcom Training Ltd. Birmingham | Mar 2022 - Aug 2022 | Clouding, Networking, IP Address, Network Maintenance etc.

**Degree** | Coventry University, | Sep 2019 - Apr 2022 | \*Software user: Autocad, Lumion, SketchUp, 3D max, Revit, Project managements \* Risk Assessment etc

**HND** | Federal Polytechnic Bida, Niger State, Nigeria | Jan 2017 - Aug 2019 | Contractor. Site Engineer, Laboratory Test, Structure Calculation.

**Diploma** | Kogi State Polytechnic, Lokoja, Nigeria. | Aug 2013 - Sep 2015 | Fundamental of Structural and Highway, Laboratory Test.

GCSE | Harmony Secondary School | May 2006 - Mar 2012

## **Additional**

### **Hobbies & Interests**

Volunteering, Sketching, Running, Cooking, Travel, Photography, Fitness, Football, Public speaking

#### Software

Microsoft office, Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Google Mail, Microsoft Windows, Adobe Photoshop

### Hardware

Networking, Printers, CPU, Routers, Servers, RAM, Mobile

#### **Programming Languages**

HTML, CSS, Java, Python, C++, C, C#

#### Languages

English, Yoruba